(Bernadette:)Howie, I think you'd have fun.
- Fine. You can tag along.
- Terrific.
My two favorite fellas "gone fishing."
(Howard:)Hang on a second.
Bernie, next weekend we have that thing.
- What thing?
- You know, the thing.
Oh, that thing. No, I canceled that thing.
(Mr. Rostenkowski:)All right, it's settled.
You and I are going fishing.
Great. Heh. Thanks for the help.
(Howard:)I've never even been fishing.
This is gonna be a disaster.
(Raj:)If you don't want to look foolish
doing something, you should practice.
(Raj:)Do you know how many beef Wellingtons
I made by myself...
(Raj:)...before I invited you guys over?
(Raj:)I'll give you a hint.
You can see them here, here and here.
Raj is right. You should get someone
to give you some pointers.